[
    {
        "question": "IS THE FACILITY SECURE?",
        "answer": "DIY HAS SEVERAL FEATURES WHICH WE ARE CONFIDENT SEPARATE US FROM OTHER FACILITIES.  PLEASE CALL FOR FURTHER DETAILS.  WE ARE GATED AND FULLY FENCED WITH REDUNDANT SECURITY CAMERAS WATCHING."
    },

    {
        "question": "HOW ARE YOUR LEASES STRUCTURED?",
        "answer": "LEASES ARE MONTH TO MONTH.  THE FIRST MONTH ONLY IS PRO-RATED.  EVERY MONTH THEREAFTER RENT IS DUE ON THE FIRST OF THE MONTH.  THERE IS A ONE FULL MONTH MINIMUM."
    },

    {
        "question": "WHEN CAN I GET IN?",
        "answer": "GATE HOURS ARE 6 AM TO 10 PM, 7 DAYS A WEEK."
    },

    {
        "question": "HOW DO I MAKE A PAYMENT? ",
        "answer": "WE ONLY USE AUTOMATIC PAYMENTS VIA CREDIT CARD OR ACH (ALSO KNOWN AS E-CHECK) VIA YOUR CHECKING ACCOUNT.   AUTOMATIC PAYMENTS ALLOW US TO AVOID CHARGING A DEPOSIT.  IF YOU WISH TO NOT PROVIDE PAYMENT AUTHORIZATION A $200 DEPOSIT OR A 6 MONTH MIN. PREPAYMENT IS REQUIRED."
    },

    {
        "question": "DO YOU OFFER ACTIVE MILITARY & FIRST RESPONDERS A DISCOUNT?",
        "answer": "WE OFFER A 5% DISCOUNT FOR ALL ACTIVE MILITARY AND FIRST RESPONDERS.    PROOF OF ACTIVE STATUS IS REQUIRED."
    },

    {
        "question": "DO YOU OFFER ANY OTHER DISCOUNTS?",
        "answer": "WE OFFER A 3% DISCOUNT FOR 6 MONTH PREPAYMENTS AND 6% DISCOUNTS FOR 12 MONTH PREPAYMENTS.  BOTH LONG TERM LEASE OPTIONS ALSO INCLUDE FREE LOCK AND WAIVED APPLICATIONS FEES.  PREPAYMENTS ARE NON-REFUNDABLE.  IF YOU ARE NOT CERTAIN YOU WILL NEED YOUR UNIT WE ASK THAT YOU STICK WITH THE MONTH-TO-MONTH LEASE OPTION.  PREPAYMENTS ARE LONG TERM LEASES.  CREDIT CARD PAYMENTS NOT ACCEPTED ON PREPAYMENTS."
    },

    {
        "question": "IS INDOOR VEHICLE OR BOAT STORAGE AVAILABLE?",
        "answer": "WE OFFER 10' X 20', 30' & 40' UNITS FOR VEHICLE STORAGE.  WE REQUIRE A VIN # & REGISTRATION FOR ALL MOTOR VEHICLES STORED ONSITE. WE ALSO NOW OFFER 10’ X 30’ TALL UNITS WITH 10’-6” TALL DOORS AND 50’ OF SURFACED SPACE TO BACK IN BOATS OR TRAILERS.  "
    },

    {
        "question": "IS MY STUFF INSURED?",
        "answer": "OUR LIST PRICES DO NOT INCLUDE INSURANCE COVERAGE OF ANY KIND.  CONSIDER CHECKING WITH YOUR INSURANCE PROVIDER TO SEE IF YOU ARE ALREADY COVERED.WE CAN PROVIDE A POLICY AT YOUR OPTION .  REGARDLESS OF WHO PROVIDES THE INSURANCE WE PREFER YOU OBTAIN RENTER'S INSURANCE. "
    },

    {
        "question": "DO I NEED A LOCK?",
        "answer": "DISK STYLE LOCKS ARE PROVIDED FREE WITH YOUR APPLICATION FEE.  YOU CAN BRING YOUR OWN LOCK OR YOU CAN USE OURS BUT THEY MUST BE A DISK STYLE LOCK.  WE ALSO OFFER DISC LOCKS AT A DISCOUNT FROM RETAIL PRICING.  PLEASE UNDERSTAND THE SECOND LOCK SLOT IS FOR OUR USE ONLY.  ONLY ONE LOCK IS ALLOWED ON THE UNIT.  IF YOU ADD A SECOND LOCK WE WILL HAVE TO CUT THE LOCK AND YOU WILL BE CHARGED FOR THE REMOVAL.  "
    },

    {
        "question": "IS TRASH OR WATER AVAILABLE ON SITE?",
        "answer": "NO"
    },

    {
        "question": "WHAT DO I NEED TO DO WHEN I TERMINATE MY LEASE?",
        "answer": "PROVIDE NOTIFICATION VIA OUR CANCEL PAGE OR  POST MARKED WRITTEN LETTER 10 DAYS PRIOR TO THE END OF THE MONTH (BE SURE TO INCLUDE YOUR UNIT #, LAST NAME AND ENTRY CODE).  BE SURE NOTICE IS PROVIDED AT LEAST 10 DAYS PRIOR TO THE END OF THE MONTH.   BE SURE TO SWEEP THE UNIT CLEAN AND AND REMOVE YOUR LOCK BEFORE THE END OF THE MONTH TO AVOID ADDITIONAL CHARGES.  "
    }
]